[SPEAKER_00]: 20 years ago, I didn't have a phone or, you know, 20, well, 24 years ago, I didn't have a phone and I was fine.
[SPEAKER_00]: Everybody was fine.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then happy you were.
[SPEAKER_01]: You were so successful.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was happy.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then it was only 15 years ago that I didn't have a smartphone.
[SPEAKER_00]: I had a flip phone.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was fine.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was fine with that.
[SPEAKER_00]: But ever since I had ever since I had a smartphone, you know But nowadays I got you go you know three hours without a smartphone and the whole thing goes to shit Jason the world changed a little too John I mean it did but you know I can understand like like last year Jason Finn asked me to go to a baseball game and On my way there.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was on the train on the way to the baseball stadium.
[SPEAKER_00]: I realized I didn't have my phone
[SPEAKER_00]: Did I tell you this story?
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: I end up at the baseball stadium, and you know, on my phone should be my ticket.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_00]: And I should also be calling Jason to tell him where I am.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you get tickets on your phone 24 years ago, John?
[SPEAKER_00]: Couldn't do it 24 couldn't do it even 15 you couldn't record it No, it was in my Apple wallet and I was gonna walk up and bloop it and then I would have texted him and he would be standing on the other side of the gate Or he would have met me out by the Ken Griffey.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I get there I got neither thing and I'm standing there thinking well He's gonna come out of the stadium and maybe he'll think that I'll be at the Ken Griffey.
[SPEAKER_00]: He'll come looking for me
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I waited and waited.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then, of course, I remember, oh, no, Jason will, he won't come looking for me.
[SPEAKER_00]: He'll sit in the, in the great seats that he got for us and he'll stew and he'll brood.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, because he's, see, see, now we got a drawing room French farce on our hands because there's been a misunderstanding and the nature of the misunderstanding is that you can't fix the misunderstanding soon.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm I'm outside standing next to the thing the game has started.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's in there stewing about the fact that I didn't come because that's consistent with what he thinks is my personality.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, he didn't even come here.
[SPEAKER_00]: And so I'm standing there by the Jersey barrier.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I say I say to the nearest I say to the nearest guy.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, hey, guy.
[SPEAKER_00]: and he comes over what?
[SPEAKER_00]: And I say, can I borrow your- I'm in town for a job interview.
[SPEAKER_00]: I need $20 for gas.
[SPEAKER_00]: I say, my alternator's broken and I hold up an alternator.
[SPEAKER_01]: My daughter's in the trunk.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I say, I say to the guy, look, there's a guy in there that's got tickets to the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: I didn't bring my phone.
[SPEAKER_00]: Can I use your phone to call my lady friend?
[SPEAKER_00]: who has the only phone number I can remember in my head right now, who also will have... Where do you keep all the phone numbers, John?
[SPEAKER_01]: Where do you keep them?
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you only just memorize them?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I keep them on my phone.
[SPEAKER_00]: I used to have them on a 3x5 card.
[SPEAKER_01]: You didn't have your phone with you, though, did you?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_00]: I used to have a 3x5 card where I wrote all my friend's phone numbers down and then I laminated it with tape.
[SPEAKER_00]: I put tape on both sides and then I put it in my chain wallet.
[SPEAKER_00]: And any time I needed to call somebody from a phone booth or something, I would pull out my tape laminated three by five card.
[SPEAKER_00]: I would look at their number and I would dial their phone number.
[SPEAKER_00]: And that's how I would call them, but I don't have that anymore.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I do have like four phone numbers, still memorized.
[SPEAKER_00]: And one of them is this phone number belonging to my daughter's mother's.
[SPEAKER_01]: If I ever need to call Empire carpeting, I'm good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because remember, service that one, that's five, eight, eight, two, 300.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Empire.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, but then they put an 800 in front of it and it's, it did kind of jam that up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, 800, five, eight, eight.
[SPEAKER_01]: I also know J.G.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wentworth can get me a structured settlement.
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know either of those guys because I, you know, that's like I've deleted that from my system folder a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: Their phone number is cash now, I think.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't even think it's recoverable, that stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, but but so so what I what I did was I called her and I said hey Will you text Jason Finn?
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry the Mariners fan will let you borrow his phone
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, and he's not happy about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's like... It kind of feels like a scam.
[SPEAKER_00]: It does.
[SPEAKER_00]: And he's like, so now this woman's phone number is gonna be in my phone?
[SPEAKER_00]: How do I know she's not gonna call me?
[SPEAKER_00]: And I'm like, look, she's a busy lady yet.
[SPEAKER_00]: She's not interested in any of this.
[SPEAKER_01]: If I had my phone, I'd show you a photo of her and you'd feel really dumb you just said that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, if I had my phone, I could tell you all about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Your dreams you get a text from her.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I say, and she says, okay, fine.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I say, tell Jason I'm out by the Ken Griffey statue.
[SPEAKER_00]: And she goes, okay, I don't know what any of this is, but you know, don't forget your phone.
[SPEAKER_00]: No time to argue.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I hand the phone back to the guy and I stand there.
[SPEAKER_00]: And sure enough, five minutes later, here comes Jason.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's, you know, he's not very impressed, but he does have the ticket on his phone.
[SPEAKER_00]: And he gets me in and the rest of the day goes without a hitch and I think John, it's still, have you, has it occurred to you?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's still required a phone.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just it was somebody else's phone.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_00]: It required a phone, but, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_00]: I was fine.
[SPEAKER_00]: It didn't, you know, it took me an extra 15 minutes of wondering what I'm going to do, but I solved the problem.